

TRAN NGOC NHU Y

Content Marketing Executive

C

0902. 390. 534

HCMC

Content Execution (Samples)

PROFILE

A passionate marketer with a love for words, planning, and campaign coordination, I aim to reach a senior level in 2 years and become a leader in 5 years. My diverse background in content, planning, and executing campaigns, combined with my dedication, drives me to continually improve and achieve impactful results in the marketing industry.

EDUCATIONVan Lang University

Bachelor of Public Relations (PR)

- Good Degree (Sep 2018 Sep 2022)
- Proficiency in English
- Marketing course on Google
- Marketing course Linkedin Learning
- Microsoft Office Certificate

Activities

- President of Academic Club <u>3N</u>
- Outstanding Student 2020, 2022
- Top 50 En Vang Hoc Duong 2020 (MC Contest)

SKILLS

Project Management

Project leader of these programs:

- The Grand Ceremony of

Best Hotels & Resorts Award 2023

Online interview article series
 of global General Managers and
 Director of Marketing & Sales

Presentation

(held in Indonesia)

Prepare documents and participate in the sharing session as a speaker about "Best Hotel & Resort Awards 2023" with students of the Faculty of Tourism and Hotel Management at RMIT Vietnam University.

Data Analysis

- Synthesize communication data to make reports after campaigns.
- Analyze and evaluate the success of social campaigns to learn from experience for future projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing Staff - Dunlopillo Vietnam

Feb 2024 - July 2024

- Manage, operate, and provide materials for the Anh Trai Say Hi program as a mattress sponsor:
- Increased brand awareness across media channels.
- Managed and tracked over 15 sponsorship activities throughout the program.
- Participate in managing and negotiating sponsorship benefits and information for the MMA Innovate 2024 program as a Gift Partner:
- Successfully negotiated 5 major sponsorship benefits.
- Secured sponsorship for over 200 gifts and 1500 shopping vouchers for the event.
- Coordinate and manage stakeholders to set up, provide materials, create memos, etc., for the NovaWorld Phan Thiết Community Connection Golf Tournament as a Diamond Sponsor:
- Managed the preparation and distribution of over 200 promotional material sets.
- Created and managed 15 cooperation memos with relevant partners.
- Achieved 100% progress and requirements for diamond sponsorship for the event.
- Manage and operate social media pages:
- Managed and operated Facebook and LinkedIn pages, increasing followers by 15%.
- Wrote and posted over 20 SEO-optimized articles, increasing website traffic by 20%.
- Achieved top 5 positions in Google search results for 5 key keywords.

Content Marketing Executive

Wanderlust Tips Magazine (Vietnam & USA)

Dec 2022 - April 2024

- Developed content for PR articles, always-on content on social networking sites and websites (WordPress).
- More than 40 PR articles published (internal and external)
- More than 1000 Website articles published
- Interviewed online and wrote interview articles for more than **10 General Managers** in 8 countries (Egypt, Mexico, Taiwan, Indonesia, Thailand, Cambodia, Maldives and Vietnam).
- Managed, promoted growth, and shaped content development across Owned Media: Website, Facebook, Tiktok, and Linked In.
- Reach: increase more than 1.5 times from 2022 to 2023 (Linked In)
- Engagement and Metrics: increase more than 1.5 times from 2022 to 2023 (Linked In)
- Average views on Tiktok: 5k 10k
- Average interactions on Tiktok: ~ 1.5k
- Planned, managed, assigned work and executed events:
- Best Hotels & Resorts Awards 2023 held in Indonesia, attracting the participation of more than
 500 influential people in the world's tourism industry, with the participation of Mrs. Ni Made Ayu Marthini,
 Deputy Minister of Marketing, Ministry of Tourism and Creative Economy of the Republic of Indonesia.
- The Art of Relaxation program with the participation of **10 leaders** in Vietnam: Mr. Agustaviano Sofjan (Consul General of Indonesia), Mr. Enrico Padula (Consul General of Italy), Mr. Fabio De Cillis (Trade Commissioner Italy),... and **20 influential guests**.
- Researched and proposed +20 suitable Kols lists for domestic and foreign Influencer Marketing Campaigns.

Communications & Content Intern ZEE Agency

Sep 2021 - Apr 2022

- Found customer insight, researched content, analyzed data, and brainstormed with the internal team after receiving client briefs.
- Proposed appropriate directions, ideas, angles, and communication channels.
- Executed communication plans, proposals and presented these plans to internal & external teams.
- Contacted, booked, and managed articles, social content from booked fan pages, and channels: S Channel, Nghien Lam Dep, Vang Xam Comic, Cafe F,...
- Collected, analyzed data and prepared weekly and monthly reports for various campaigns: Tiger Balm, OCB,...
- Wrote PR articles, captions, scripts and monitored recording sessions to ensure the quality for a variety of campaigns from Comfort, Sunlight, Pond, VIB 2.0,...

Script Editor & Communications Intern T Production

Oct 2020 - Feb 2021

- Planned, created ideas, and content for projects: The reality show "Một Chuyến Đi", TV show "Ngày May Mắn", Music program "Gala Nhạc Việt số 15".
- Interviewed artists, and got materials for media articles.
- Managed fanpages, supported social team to implement communication ideas: Gala Nhạc Việt fanpage, Việt Nam Tươi Đẹp fanpage, Ngày May Mắn fanpage.
- Supported the production team during on-set: Showcase "Rồi Một Ngày Hà Nói Về Tình Yêu", MV "Tết Nhà Mình", Mashup "Đã Sai Từ Lúc Đầu & Cạn Dòng Nước Mắt".